Phone: 226 - 920 - 6244

Email: vuxx9640@mylaurier.ca

Portfolio Website: https://vu-michael.github.io/Portfolio-Website/

GitHub: https://github.com/VU-MICHAEL

Michael Vu

Objective:

I am a reliable, respectful, and motivated university student with interest of building experience in the workforce. I am able to learn new tasks quickly, proficient in growing key customer relationships, and can handle tasks effectively and efficiently with great attention to detail.

SKILLS

- Excellent written and spoken communication skills
- Good at following tasks
- Knowledge of useful design patterns
- Fast learning ability

 Proficient at working in a team and individually

EXPERIENCE

07/2019 - 09/2020	 Summer Student TCBA Member, Toyota Boshoku Woodstock, Ontario Performed well under a constantly stressful environment Worked as part of a successful team Performed tasks well that required great attention to detail
02/2021 - 09/2021	Dairy/Frozen associate, Walmart Brantford, Ontario
	Working in fast-paced environment
	 Stocking dairy/frozen and maintaining shelves
	 Demonstrated strong interpersonal skills while dealing with customers
	Organizing skids
07/2019 - 09/2020	Bakery Clerk, Zehrs Brantford, Ontario
	 Working in fast-paced environment
	 Keep bakery stocked up, rotate products, and scan out expired product.
	Organizing freezer and skids

EDUCATION

Graduated 2020 High School Diploma, St Johns College | Brantford, Ontario

2021 – Present Bachelor of Science in Computer Science, Wilfrid Laurier University |
Waterloo, Ontario

Projects and Technical Skills

IT Essentials Certification, cisco, June 17th, 2019 **Cybersecurity Essentials**, cisco, November 4th, 2020